Guide to the Leonard Solomon Silk papers, 1929-1995 and undated, bulk 1950-1985 RL.01187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 6096, 1933-1985, and undated, 86 boxes
  - Speeches and Addresses (Box 106)
    - Culver, J., (Senator), before the American Assembly on Corporate Governance, Columbia University, New York City, April 13, 1978, no title (Box 106)
    - Debs, R. A., before the 10th Annual Convention of the Banking Law Institute, International Banking, New York City, May 8, 1975 (Box 106)
    - Dubos, R. L., Learning to Live with Less Energy, before the Second National Symposium of the Rene Dubos Forum, September 24, 1978 (Box 106)
    - Friedman, Milton (Dr.), The Source of Strength, before the Presidents' Club of Michigan General Corporation, New Orleans, Louisiana, April 2, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Georgescu-Roegan, N., The Entropy Law and the Economic Problem, delivered December 3, 1970, Distinguished Lecture Series, No. 1, Department of Economics, The Graduate School of Business and Office for International Programs, The University of Alabama (Box 106)
    - Handler, P., On the State of Man, before the Annual Convocation of Markel Scholars, September 29, 1974 (Box 106)
    - Jawdat, N. A., Cheap Energy, Diversification of Sources and Security of Supply, at the Loughborough College of Technology, November 24, 1965 (Box 106)
    - Kagan, S., A New International Economic Order: What is the Price Tag? before the Annual Meeting of the National Association of Business Economist, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, October 10, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Kaufman, H., Reflections on Economic Judgments, Given to a group of Delegates and Guests Attending the Annual Meeting of the International Bank for Reconstruction and Affiliates of the International Monetary Fund, at the International Club of Washington, D.C., September 28, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Leontief, Wassily, The Anatomy of Planning, before the Plenary Conference on Economic Growth, Canadian Manufacturer's Association Annual General Meeting, Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, Monday, June 3, 1963, 2 copies (Box 106)
    - Minsky, H. P., T he Current State of the American Economy, before a session of the Midwest Economics Association, Chicago, Illinois, April 4, 1975 (Box 106)
    - Parsky, G., The Energy Crisis and Economic Development in the Middle East, University Seminar on the Middle East, Columbia University, 13 November 1974, New York City (Box 106)
    - Rice, D. B., New Institutions for Social and Economic Regulation, before the Symposium on Business-Management Partnership, LBJ Library, University of Texas, no date (Box 106)
    - Smith, Roger B., no title, at the Symposium on Business and Government, March 2, 1979, no location (Box 106)
    - Samuelson, P. A., International Trade for a Rich Country, before the Swedish-American Chamber of Commerce, New York City, May 10, 1972 (Box 106)
    - Maximum Principles in Analytical Economics, Nobel Memorial Lecture, December 11, 1970 (Box 106)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Good Sense and Bad Data, before the Market Research Council, New York City, December 15, 1972 (Box 106)
    - Simon, H. A., Rationality as Process and as Product of Thought, American Economic Association Winter Meeting, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Wallich, H. C>, The Impact of Inflation on Financial Institutions, at the Meeting of the Banking Chair Holders, The American Bankers Association, Watergate Hotel, Washington, D. C., January 6, 1975 (Box 106)
    - Weber, A. R., A Wage-Price Freeze as an Instrument of Incomes Policy, or the Blizzard of '71, for a Joint Session of the Industrial Research Association and the American Economic Association, New Orleans, December 27, 1971 (Box 106)
    - Weintraub, S., The Keynesian Light that Failed, The University of Pennsylvania, February 1975 (Box 106)
    - A Theory of Monetary Policy Under Wage Inflation, The University of Queensland, 10 July 1974 (Box 106)
    - No author, Private Interests and Public Policy, no location, no date (Box 106)
    - No author, Welcome Banquet Secretary Krep's Toast, no location, no date (Box 106)
  - Statements (Box 106)
    - Apel, H., (Hon.), Statement at the Joint Annual Discussion Boards of Governors, 1977 Annual Meetings, Washington D.C., September 27, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Blumenthal, W. M., Statement, no date (Box 106)
    - Secretary Bluemnthal's Press Statement in Rome, Italy, October 31, 1977 (Box 106)
    - Burns, Arthur F.
      - Statement before the Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy and the Subcommittee on International Exchange and Payments of the Joint Economic Committee, June 30, 1971 (Box 106)
      - Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, July 23, 1971-Feb. 20, 1973, 4 items (Box 106)
      - Statement before the Joint Study on Budget Control, March 6, 1973 (Box 106)
      - Statement before the Committee on Banking and Currency, House of Representatives, March 7, 1973 (Box 106)
      - Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, August 6, 1974 (Box 106)
      - Statement before the Committee on Ways and Means, January 30, 1975 (Box 106)
      - Statement before the Subcommittee on Domestic Monetary Policy of the Committee on Banking, Currency and Housing, February 6, 1975 (Box 106)
    - Enders, T. O., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, 29 November 1974 (Box 106)
    - Kuehner, C. D., Capital Formation -- Inflation and Jobs, Statement before the Joint Economic Committee of the Congress of the United States, Washington, D.C., July 11, 1978 (Box 106)
    - Mitchell, D.J.B., Statement before the Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, November 3, 1978 (Box 106)
    - Perry, G. L., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, February 7, 1979 (Box 106)
    - The Business Round Table, Statement, The Role and Composition of the Board of Directors of the Large Publicly Owned Corporation, January 1978 (Box 106)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Statement, The Economy, 1977-1978, December 1976 (Box 106)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Key Elements of a National Energy Strategy, June 1977 (Box 106)
  - Testimony (Box 106)
    - Feldstein, M., Testimony given to the House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, February 22, 1979 (Box 106)
    - Vojta, G. J., Testimony before the Subcommittee on African Affairs of the Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, September 23, 1976 (Box 106)
  - Documents (Box 108)
    - Lyon, L. S., and Abramson, V., Government and Economic Life, Vol. 2, Washington, D.C., The Brookings Institution, 1940 (Box 108)
    - Mahoney, T., The Story of George Romney, Builder, Salesman, Crusader, New York, Harper, 1960, 1st ed (Box 108)
    - Silk, Leonard S. and Silk, M., The American Establishment, New York, Basic Books, 1980 (Box 108)
    - The Economists, New York, Basic Books, Through Charles E. Tuttle Inc., Tokyo, 1976 (In Japanese) (Box 108)
    - Silk, Leonard S. and Vogel, D., Ethics and Profits, New York, Simon and Schuester through Japan UNI Agency, Inc., 1976 (In Japanese) (Box 108)
    - Saunders, P., The World of Economics, Study Guide and Workbook to Accompany 'The World of Economics,' by Leonard S. Silk and Phillip Saunders (Box 108)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Economics in Plain English: All You Need to Know About Economics -- In Language Anyone Can Understand, New York, Simon and Schuster, 1978 (Box 108)
    - Silk, Leonard S., with the assistance of Curley, M. L., Forecasting Business Trends, New York, McGraw-Hill, 1963 (Box 108)
    - OS Economistas, Rio de Janeiro, Zahar Editores, 1976 (in Portuguese) (Box 108)
  - Catalogs (Box 109)
    - The Evolution of Capitalism, books, 3 copies (Box 109)
    - The Evolution of Capitalism, publicity flier, 1972 (Box 151)
    - The Trilateral Commission, A Private North American-European-Japanese Initiative on Matters of Common Concern (Box 109)
    - University of Stockholm, Institute for International Economic Studies, 1980/1981 (Box 109)
  - Charts, 3 items (Box 109)
  - Correspondence, 11 November, 1970 - 10 November 1980, and undated (Box 109)
    Includes correspondence between Leonard S. Silk and important academic, political, and economic figures such as Don Congdon, Paul A. Schosberg, Edward M. Kennedy, William Woodward, Hedley Donovan, Bob Nero, Daniel J. Meltzer, Rawleigh Warner Jr., Bayless Manning, and Franklin Lindsay.
  - Directory (Box 109)
    - New York Times Telephone Directory, July 1976 (Box 109)
  - Dissertation (Box 109)
  - Kellner, I. L., The American Cigarette Industry, Dissertation, Abstract, New School for Social Research, Economics, Graduate Faculty, June, 1973 (Box 109)
  - Documents (Box 109)
    - Arab Republic of Egypt, Law no. 43 of 1974, Concerning the Investment of Arab and Foreign Funds and the Free Zones as Amended by Law no. 32, of 1977 (Box 109)
    - Economic Report of the President, transmitted to the congress January 1978, Washington, United States Government Printing Offict, 1978 (Box 109)
    - Fiscal Containment of Local and State Government, prepared under a grant from Ford Foundation, by Anthony, and others, Rand report, R-2494-FF/RC, September, 1979 (Box 109)
    - National Commission on Employment and Unemployment Statistics, Public Law 94-444, October 1, 1976 (Box 109)
    - United Nations, Economic and Social Council, Transnational Corporations in World Development, United Nations, 1978 (Box 109)
    - U.S. 95th Congress, 1st Session, Economic Indications, Washington, D.C., U.S. Govt. Printing Off., 1977 (Box 109)
    - U.S. 96th Congress, 1st Session, Report of the Committee on Ways and Means, House of Representatives, Washington, D.C., Government Printing Office, 1979 (Box 109)
  - Documents (Box 110)
    - U.S. 96th Congress, 2nd Session, Staff Report on Corporate Accountability, Washington, D.C., U.S. Govt. Printing Office, 1980 (Box 110)
    - U.S. 96th Congress, 2nd Session, Tax Policy and Core Inflation, Washington, D.C., U.S. Govt. Printing Office, 1980 (Box 110)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, BLS Measures of Compensation, Washington, D.C., U.S. Govt. Printing Off., 1977, Bulletin, 1941 (Box 110)
    - U.S. Dept. of State, Trade Relations - Agreement Between the United States of America and the Hungarian People's Republic, signed at Budapest March 17, 1978, xerox (Box 110)
    - U.S. Dept. of the Treasury, Blueprints for Basic Tax Reform, January 17, 1977 (Box 110)
    - U.S. Dept. of the Treasury, The President's 1978 Tax Program, Washington, D.C., Dept of the Treasury, January 30, 1978 (Box 110)
    - U.S. Executive Office of the President, Office of Management and Budget, The Budget of the United States Government, Fiscal year 1973 (Box 110)
    - U.S. Executive Office of the President, Office of Management and Budget, Fiscal Year 1978, Budget Revisions, February 1977 (Box 110)
  - Documents (Box 111)
    - U.S. Executive Office of the President, Office of Management and Budget, Special Analyses Budget of the United States Government, Fiscal year 1979 (Box 111)
    - U.S. Executive Office of the President, Office of Management and Budget, Special Analyses Budget of the United States Government, Fiscal year 1980 (Box 111)
    - U.S. Supreme Court of the United States, no. 76-1172, First National Bank of Boston et al., Appellants Vs. Francis X. Bellotti, etc., et al., April 26, 1978 (Box 111)
  - Drafts (Box 111)
    - Public Policy and the Market System, September 1, 1978, prepared by the Subcommittee on Regulation and the Role of Government in the Economy, 4 pages, plus memorandum (Box 111)
    - Chapter I: Summary of Analysis and Recommendations. (Box 111)
    - Chapter II: The Market Mechanism and the Role of Government, 16 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter III: The Extent and Nature of Government Involvement in the Economy, 19 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter IV: Needed: A Better Relationship Between Government and the Market, 8 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter V: Criteria for Government Involvement in the Economy, 11 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter VI: Alternative Methods of Government Involvement, 28 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter VII: A More Systematic Decision-Making Process, 29 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter VIII: National Commitment to Economic Growth, 1 page (Box 111)
    - Chapter 5: Improving Television Performance with Limited Channels, draft 2, 29 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter 6: Improving Television Performance with Limited Channels, draft 2, B.M. Owen, 30 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter 7: Public Television, draft 2, B.M. Owen, 24 pages (Box 111)
    - Chapter 8: Policy Issues, draft 1, B.M. Owen, 18 pages (Box 111)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Business Power, Today and Tomorrow, Boston, Board of the Academy, 1968, unedited draft (Box 111)
  - Interviews (Box 111)
    Interviews conducted by Silk of various notable individuals in politics or finance.
    - Byrom, Fletcher, 2 copies, September 12, 1979 (Box 111)
    - Eberstadt, Walter, October 30 [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Evans, James H., November 22, 1978 (Box 111)
    - File, Lucien Toney, November 27 [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Finn, David, December 21, 1978 (Box 111)
    - Freund, William, Dr., October 18 [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Kinney, Richard, November 28, 1978 (Box 111)
    - Oakes, John B., 2 copies, June 15, 1979 (Box 111)
    - O'Leary, Jim, Dr., October 18, [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Rogow, Arnold, November 30, 1978, 2 copies (Box 111)
    - Rockefeller, David, undated (Box 111)
    - Samuels, Nathaniel, October 16, [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Schmertz, Herbert, October 23, [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs, June 18, 1979, June 25, 1979, 2 copies (Box 111)
    - Thompson, Tommy, October 12, [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Unwin, Richmond, October 6, [n.y.] (Box 111)
    - Wallace, Martha, November 1 [n.y.] (Box 111)
  - Kits (Box 112)
    - The American Assembly (Mr. Silk), 17 items (Box 112)
    - The Business Roundtable, July 1977, 56 items (Box 112)
    - Jobs for the Hard to Employ, 6 items (Box 112)
    - Joint Council on Economic Education (Leonard Silk), 12 items (Box 112)
  - Lists (Box 112)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Advisory Ad Hoc Committee on Corporate Planning and Government, undated (Box 112)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Subcommittee on Employment for the Young, Old, Disadvantaged and Displaced, November, 1977 (Box 112)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Subcommittee on Revitalizing America's Cities, November 1977 (Box 112)
    - The Ford Foundation, Economic Policy Meeting, Participants (Box 112)
    - Subcommittee on Regulation and the Role of Government Intervention in the Economy ..., Attendance, September 19, 1978. (Box 112)
    - The Trilateral Commission, September 1, 1973 (Box 112)
  - Mailgrams, 3 items (Box 112)
  - Manuals (Box 112)
    - Kersten, T., Instructor's Manual to Accompany Contemporary Economics, by Silk, Principles and Issues, 2nd ed., New York, McGraw-Hill, 1975, 2 copies (Box 112)
    - Saunders, P., Welsh, A. L., and Hansen, W. L., [editors], Resource Manual for Teaching Programs in Economics, New York, Joint Council on Economic Education, 1978 (Box 112)
  - Manuscripts (Box 113-114)
    - Manuscript pages and research material for The American Establishment, by Leonard Silk and Mark Silk, 1660 pages (in no specific order) (Box 113-114)
  - Manuscripts (Box 115)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Economics, for Sunday/Week in Review, 12 [i.e. 13] pages, carbon, annotated (Box 115)
    - The Economics of Kenneth Boulding, 15 pages, original, annotated (Box 115)
    - Economics of the Met, for Bill Honan/Sunday Arts and Leisure, 21 pages, original, annotated (Box 115)
    - Ideals in Collision, 2 items, 11 pages (incomplete) original, annotated; 29 pages, xerox, annotated (Box 115)
    - Silk's Comment on Shaw's Comment on Olive Bell's Article, July 5, 1977, 1 page, 3 copies, original and 2 xerox (Box 115)
    - The New York Times: Church, State and the Counting House, 18 pages, incomplete, original, annotated (Box 115)
    - Unidentified manuscript pages, 19 pages, xerox, annotated (Box 115)
  - Memoranda (Box 115)
    - To Subcommittee on Controlling the New Inflation, from John R. Coleman, May 7, 1975 (Box 115)
    - To Leonard Silk, from Max Frankel, April 30, 1976 (Box 115)
    - To Mr. Oakes, from A.O. Sulzberger, March 18, 1976 (Box 115)
    - To Aspen Institute Friends and Family, from Joseph E. Slater, December 1, 1977 (Box 115)
    - To Subcommittee on Improving the Long-term performance of the U.S. Economy, Franklin A. Lindsay, December 6, 1977 (Box 115)
    - To Research and Policy Committee..., from Franklin A. Lindsay, May 5, 1978 (Box 115)
    - To Research Advisory Board, from Robert C. Holland, May 23, 1978 (Box 115)
    - To Robert C. Holland, from Hugh Stier, May 31, 1978 (Box 115)
    - To Leonard Silk, from Sandra Coppola, April 4, 1980 (Box 115)
    - To no name, from Ruben F. Mettler, October, 1980 (Box 115)
    - To Persons Interested in Tax Reform, from Tom Field, undated (Box 115)
  - Minutes (Box 115)
    - Minutes of the Research and Policy Committee, 21 May, 1975 (Box 115)
  - News and Press Releases (Box 115)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York, World Financial Markets, November 25, 1977 (Box 115)
    - News from the AFL-CIO, December2, 1977 (Box 115)
    - News of Athenaeum Publishers. (Box 115)
    - Bache News, November 30, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States News. (Box 115)
    - Conference Board, Information of the Press, May 23, 1980 (Box 115)
    - Conference on Economic Progress, June 16, 1980 (Box 115)
    - Congressional Quarterly News Service, August 16, 1976 (Box 115)
    - Dick Gruenwald Associates News, November 30, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, November 30 1977 (Box 115)
    - Frederick Fell, Inc., Book Publisher (Box 115)
    - Free Press News, 5 Pieces (Box 115)
    - General Motors Corporation News, December 2, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Grace News, May 27, 1980 (Box 115)
    - Houghton Mifflin Release, March 1, 1979 (Box 115)
    - News/Crown, 3 pieces (Box 115)
    - News/Harmony, 2 pieces (Box 115)
    - News from John Wiley and Sons, Inc (Box 115)
    - Macmillan News. (Box 115)
    - MIT Press release, Robert Schrank: Ten Thousand Working Days (Box 115)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, November 25, 1977 (Box 115)
    - National Planning Association News, October 15, 1979 (Box 115)
    - Peter H. Wyden, Inc. News, September 19, n.y (Box 115)
    - Pleneum Publishing Corporation Release: The Ford Foundation at Work. (Box 115)
    - Publication of a new Resource Manual for Teacher Training Programs in Economics, December 9, 1978 (Box 115)
    - News from Simon and Schuester, 2 pieces (Box 115)
    - News from Summit Books. (Box 115)
    - Taxation with Representation, Leading Tax Experts Call for Repeal of Disc Export Subsidy, June 17, 1976 (Box 115)
    - Taxation with Representation, Senate Rated on Tax Reform, July 19, 1976 (Box 115)
    - Treasury and Federal Reserve Foreign Exchange Operation, December 1, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Twentieth Century Fund News, May 24, 1977 (Box 115)
    - World Future Society News, September 30, 1979 (Box 115)
    - Aspen Institute Chronicle, no. 10, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Barron's The Market Week, April 18, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Bostian Research Associates, Vol. 1, no. 1 February 23, 1977 (Box 115)
    - British Record, no. 14, November 30, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Donaldson, Lufkin and Jenrette, Economic Notes; A Weekly Publication, December 1, 1977 (Box 115)
    - ", December 2, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Economic Research Department, Weekly Economic Package, November 29, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Economic Week, November 28, 1977 (Box 115)
    - IPS Transnational Link, no. 13, February 1976 (Box 115)
    - International Tax News, vol. 6, no. 4, October, 1980 (Box 115)
    - Loeb Rhoades and Co., Economic Comment, November 22, 1977, no. 15 (Box 115)
    - National Review, November 13, 1977 (Box 115)
    - New York University, The Bulletin, 1976-3 (Box 115)
    - Public Citizen People and Taxes, vol. IV, no. 5, May, 1976 (Box 115)
    - Public Employee Press, vol. XXI, no. 19, October 31, 1980 (Box 115)
    - Public Interest Economics, vol. 2, no. 2, February 15, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Taxation with Representation Newsletter, vol. 5, no. 2, March 1, 1976 (Box 115)
    - World Financial Markets, November, 1977 (Box 115)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Newspaper Sections (Box 116)
    - Newspaper clippings: articles by Leonard Silk on economics, 28 items (Box 116)
    - Newspaper clippings and newspaper sections, 34 items (Box 116)
  - Pamphlets (Box 116)
    - Academy for Educational Development, New York, undated (Box 116)
    - Camps, M., The Case for a New Global Trade Organization, New York, Council on Foreign Relations, Inc., 1980, plus 1 attachment (Box 116)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Revitalizing the Federal Personnel System, 1978 (Box 116)
    - Deloitte, H., Sells, USA, Personal Tax and Financial Planning..., 1980 (Box 116)
    - The Egypt-U.S. Business Council, Investment Stimulation Program, January, 1977 (Box 116)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, Fedpoints, nos. 1,3,4,8,9,10, Public Information Dept., December 1977 (Box 116)
    - Golembe Associates presents National Conference on Competition in Banking, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 116)
    - Hoover, Herbert, American Ideals Versus the New Deal, Scribner Press, [193-?] (Box 116)
    - Irving, Trust Company, Business Conditions, USA, Winter, 1977 (Box 116)
    - Lapp, R. E., Space Science, American Library Association, 1962 (Box 116)
    - McNamara, R. S., Address to the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, MA, April 28, 1977 (Box 116)
    - Ministry of Planning, Central Statistical Office, Kuwait Review, 1977 (Box 116)
    - Montclair Public Library, January 1, 1980 (Box 116)
    - The New York Stock Exchange, Building a Better Future, Economic Choices for the 1980s (Box 116)
    - Ras Tanura Refinery, Dhahran, Saudi Arabia, August 1976, in English and Arabic (Box 116)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, Purpose and Program, undated (Box 116)
    - Tacation with Representation, Comprehensive Tax Reform Voting Scale, October 20, 1976 (Box 116)
    - The United States Council, 1979-1980 (Box 116)
    - URPE (Union for Radical Political Economics), undated (Box 116)
  - Papers (Box 117)
    - Beebe, J. H., and Owen, Bruce M., Alternative Structures for Television, Staff research paper, November 1972 (Box 117)
    - Institutional Structure and Program Choices in Television and Cable Television Markets, Stanford, CA, Research Center in Economic Growth, August, 1972, memorandum no. 131 (Box 117)
    - Bernstein-Macaulay, Inc., Is the Herd Wrong Again? December 1, 1977 (Box 117)
    - Brinner, R. and Alexander, M., The Role of High-Technology Industries in Economic Growth, March 15, 1977 (Box 117)
    - Brown, T. R., et al, Interdisciplinary Study of the Mass Media, Stanford University, August, 1971 (Box 117)
    - Cohen, K. J., Maier, S. F., and Vander Weide, J. H., Recent Developments in Management Science in Banking, presented at 24th International Meeting of TIMS, Honolulu, Hawaii, June 18-22, 1979 (Box 117)
    - Committee for Economic Development, North-South Relations, Developing a Constructive Response to Demands for a New Economic Order, May, 1975 (Box 117)
    - Problems of National Planning, May, 1975 (Box 117)
    - Proposed Design Committee on International Trade Issues, May 5, 1978, plus attachment (Box 117)
    - Research and Policy Committee, November 17, 1977 (Box 117)
    - (Lindsay, F. A.), Report of the Research and Policy Committee, May 1978 (Box 117)
    - Topical Agenda of Past and Future Subcommittee Meetings, May, 1975 (Box 117)
    - Training and Jobs Programs in Action: Case Studies in Private Sector Initiatives for the Hard-to-Employ, New York, Committee for Economic Development, January 12, 1978, 2 copies (Box 117)